Guide to the William J. Baumol Papers, 1928-2013 and undated RL.00092
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1946-2012 and undated
  - Articles, Book Chapters, and Other Papers, 1946-2012 and undated; 1
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism, and Economic Applications, 1987-1988; 45 unidentified and document files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0046)
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism, and Economic Applications, 1985-1987; 20 text and unidentified files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0009)
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism, and Economic Applications, 1987; 17 files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0013)
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism, and Economic Applications, 1987; 16 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0014)
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism, and Economic Applications, 1983-1989; 11 document (Lotus 1-2-3 format) and still image (HP Vector Graphic) files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0083)
    - Chaos: Significance, Mechanism, and Economic Applications, 1983-1987; 10 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0116)
    - Chapter 1: Productivity Growth and the Long Run View in Economics, 1984 (Box 4)
    - Chapter for Handbook of the Economics of Art and Culture, 2005 (Box 45)
      Proof, draft, and correspondence
    - Children of Performing Arts, The Economic Dilemma, 1996 (Box 45)
    - Chinese Cuisine Book, Undated (Box 4)
    - Clare Market Review Summer 1947 (Box 45)
    - Classical Monetary Theory: The Outcome of the Discussion, 1952; 2 folders (Box 45)
    - Closing the Technology Gap, undated (Box 45)
    - Collier's Ency Contribution, 1993 (Box 45)
    - Comments on Sidak-Spilbur Article, 1994-1996 (Box 24)
      Draft paper responding to paper by Sidak and Spilbur on breaches of regulations for the American Enterprise Institute
    - Commission on New Technological Uses of Copyrighted Work, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
      Draft report on property rights and computer software
    - Community Indifference, 1946-1947 (Box 45)
    - Company Goals, Growth, and the Multiproduct Firm, 1962-1964 (Box 45)
    - Comparative U.S. Productivity Performance and the State of Manufacturing, 1992 (Box 45)
    - Competition and Monopoly in Telecommunications Services, 1970 (Box 45)
    - Competition Policy in Dynamic Markets, 2001 (Box 37)
    - Competition vs. Research, 1983 (Box 26)
    - Competitive Highway-User fees for trucks, 1989 (Box 23)
    - Competitive Interdependence in Decision Making, undated (Box 46)
    - Competitive Pricing and the Centralized Market Place, 1974 (Box 45)
    - Competitive Rail Regulation Rules, 1996; 2 folders (Box 37)
      Copy and drafts
    - Competitive Rail Regulation Rules, 1999 (Box 46)
    - Concentrazione industriale, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Condition and needs of the live professional theatre in America, 1978 (Box 19)
    - Consumers' and Producers' Surplus vs Externality Effects of Innovation, 1978 (Box 46)
    - Containing medical costs: why price controls won't work, undated (Box 46)
    - Contestability: Development since the Book, 1985-1987; 2 folders (Box 2)
      Drafts and related correspondence
    - Contestability: Developments Since the Book, undated (Box 46)
    - Contestability: Developments Since the Book, 1987; 3 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0101)
    - Contestability: Developments Since the Book, 1983-1986; 5 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0105)
    - Contestable Markets, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Contestable Markets and the Theory of Industry Structure: A Review Article, 1982-1983 (Box 46)
    - Contestable Markets, Antitrust and Regulation, 1982 (Box 46)
    - Contestable Markets, Trade, and Development, 1990 (Box 2)
    - Contestable Markets, Trade, and Development, 1989; 3 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0007)
    - Contestable Markets: An Uprising in the Theory of Industry Structure, 1981; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Contribution to Famous Figures and Diagrams in Economics, 2008 (Box 46)
    - Contribution to Oxford Handbook of Capitalism, 2009 (Box 46)
    - Contributions to a Reader's Guide to Social Sciences, 1999 (Box 38)
    - Convergence of Productivity - Artwork, undated (Box 83)
      Includes proofs of graphs and other figures for publication on international convergence of productivity
    - Convergence: its significance and its varied connotations, 1992 (Box 25)
    - Convergence: Its Significance and its Varied Connotations, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Conversation with William Baumol, 2003 (Box 25)
      Copy of interview with Baumol
    - Conzentrazione industriale, 1992 (Box 4)
    - Corporation and the Financial Problem of the Cities, 1968 (Box 46)
    - Cost and Profit Outlook, 1955-1959 (Box 46)
      Includes newsletters distributed by Alderson and Sessions - Marketing and Management Counsel
    - Cost Disease of Personal Services and the Quality of Life, 1972 (Box 29)
    - Cost Disease of the Personal Service: A Primer for Education Planners and Administrators, 1995 (Box 37)
      Draft and notes
    - Cost Minimizing Number of Firms and Determination of Industry Structure, 1976-1978; 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 2005 (Box 46)
    - Decision Making Under Uncertainty, 1957 (Box 46)
    - Decomposition Pricing for Decentralization, 1964 (Box 84)
    - Decomposition, Pricing for Decentralization and External Economies, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Demand for Abstract Transport Modes: Some Hopes, 1969 (Box 46)
    - Demand for Abstract Transport Modes: Theory and Measurement, 1966 (Box 46)
    - Depreciation, 1969 (Box 34)
    - Deregulation and the New Contestability Analysis, 1982 (Box 46)
    - Deregulation and the Theory of Contestable Markets, 1983 (Box 46)
    - Deregulatory Takings, 1997 (Box 29)
      Proofs
    - Deregulatory Takings, Breach of the Regulatory Contract, and the Telecommunications Act of 1992, 1997 (Box 46)
    - Design issues for health-care programs and the problem of rising costs, 1994 (Box 14)
    - Desindustrialization: myth or reality?, Undated (Box 4)
    - Determinants of Industry structure and contestable market theory, 1991 (Box 6)
    - Development and Entrepreneurship, 1992 (Box 14)
    - Development of large international research programs, 1996 (Box 36)
    - Development of Large International Research Programs, 1996 (Box 36)
    - Development, Global Change and the Epidemiological Environment: A Few Remarks, 1995 (Box 25)
    - Discrimination and Market Power, 2000 (Box 24)
    - Discussion Paper Series, 1975-1985; 5 folders (Box 55)
      Includes working paper versions of various papers by Baumol
    - Do Health Care Costs Matter, 1993 (Box 46)
    - Do Old fallacies ever die? A few Comments, 1993 (Box 23)
    - Does the Constitution Require That We Kill the Competitive Goose, 1998 (Box 46)
    - Downsizing, Undated (Box 34)
    - Downsizing and some possible consequences for employment, inequality, and profits, 1996; 7 folders (Box 38)
      Includes drafts and related materials for paper funded by Russell Sage Foundation
    - Dr. Marx, Dr. Frankenstein, and Mr. Ricardo, 1998 (Box 38)
    - Draft paper on antitrust, 1990; 2 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0026)
    - Draft paper on international productivity comparisons, 1987; 11 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0025)
    - Draft paper on J.B. Say, 1983-1986; 9 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0104)
    - Draft paper on productivity, 1983-1987; 12 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0102)
    - Draft paper on regulation, 1983-1987; 14 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0114)
    - Draft paper on value of art, 1983-1986; 7 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0103)
    - Draft papers on allocative efficiency and contestable markets, 1990; 6 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0027)
    - Draft papers on entrepreneurship, productivity growth, and contestable markets, 1983-1986; 12 text files; less than 1 MB (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0099)
    - Draft papers on sectoral productivity, 1987; 4 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0098)
    - Draft writings on Adam Smith, new economics, and Palgrave entry on economies of scale in financial activities, 1990; 8 document and text files (Lotus-1-2-3 and plain text formats); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0029)
    - Draft writings on entrepreneurship, 1984-1987; 7 unidentified files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0097)
    - Dual in Nonlinear Programming and its Economic Interpretation, 1968 (Box 46)
      Reprint and proofs
    - Dynamic Programming, Undated (Box 34)
    - Dynamics and Statics in Economics, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Dynamics of Urban Problems and its Policy Implications, 1972 (Box 46)
    - Early Mathematical Economics According to Jevons, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Economic Background of Business, 1964 (Box 46)
    - Economic Diagnosis for Health System, 2010 (Box 46)
    - Economic Education and the Critics of Mainstream Economics, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Economic Education for a Half-Century of Radical Change, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
      Drafts, proofs, and related correspondence
    - Economic models and mathematics, undated (Box 46)
    - Economic Processes and Policies, 1954 (Box 46)
    - Economic Theory and the Political Scientists, 1954 (Box 46)
    - Economically Defensible access pricing, competition and preservation of socially desirable cross subsidy, 2001 (Box 25)
    - Economically Defensible access pricing, competition and preservation of socially desirable cross subsidy, 2001 (Box 26)
    - Economics, 2001; 2 folders (Box 25)
      Contribution to Mathematics Education Encyclopedia
    - Economics, 1967 (Box 46)
      Draft and reprint of Encyclopedia Britannica entry written by Baumol
    - Economics for Peterson's Guide, 1992 (Box 1)
      Draft contribution for Peterson's Guide
    - Economics of Athenian Drama, 1971 (Box 46)
    - Economics of Athenian Drama: its Relevance for the Arts in a Small City Today, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Economics of Musical Composition in Mozart's Vienna, 1992; 4 folders (Box 6)
      Drafts and related correspondence for paper co-authored with Hilda Baumol
    - Economics of Property Rights, 1977 (Box 29)
    - Economics of War Article, 2007 (Box 38)
      Includes materials for article on economics of terrorism and nuclear weapons
    - Economics, Peterson's Guides, 1992 (Box 46)
    - Economies of Scale in Financial Activities, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Economists and Innovators: Practical Products of Theoretical Research, 1986-1988; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Economists and the Business Community, Undated (Box 3)
    - Economists as Innovators: Practical Products of Theoretical Research, 1987 (Box 3)
    - Economists as Innovators: Practical Products of Theoretical Research, 1988 (Box 13)
      Galley proofs
    - Education for Innovation: Entrepreneurial Breakthroughs vs Corporate Incremental Improvements, 2004 (Box 46)
    - Education in Economics: Evidence on Determinants of Effectiveness, 1989; 2 folders (Box 3)
      Includes drafts and related correspondence
    - Education's effect on productivity, 1986-1992; 2 folders (Box 1)
      Drafts and research materials
    - Efficiency Incentives, Inflation and Regulation, 1983 (Box 25)
    - Efficiency of Corporate Investment, 1973 (Box 46)
    - Electronics, Costs, and the Operation of Libraries, 1981-1983 (Box 46)
    - Electronics, the Cost Disease, and the Operation Libraries, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Electronics, the cost disease, and the operation of libraries, 1984 (Box 29)
    - Emission Permits vs Emission Charges, 1978 (Box 46)
      Draft and research report
    - Empirical Evaluation of Educational Practices: The Contribution of Economics, 1991 (Box 46)
    - Empirical Study of Scale Economies and Production Complementarity, 1977 (Box 46)
    - Endogenous Dissemination of Technology and North-South Divergence, 2003 (Box 46)
    - Enlightened Self-Interest and Corporate Philanthropy, undated (Box 46)
    - Enterprise et Societe, undated (Box 46)
    - Enterprising Rent Seeking: The Case of Corporate Takeovers, 1990-1991 (Box 2)
    - Entrepreneurial Enterprises, 2004 (Box 26)
    - Entrepreneurial Cultures and Countercultures for Swedish Learning and Educational Journal, 2003 (Box 46)
    - Entrepreneurial Enterprises, Large Established Firms and Other Components of the Free-Market Growth Machine, 2004 (Box 46)
    - Entrepreneurial Growth: Why Some Economies Grow and Others Don't, 2004 (Box 46)
    - Entrepreneurs, Inventors and the Growth of the Economy, 2006 (Box 25)
    - Entrepreneurs, Inventors and the Growth of the Economy, 2006 (Box 46)
    - Entrepreneurship and a Century Growth, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Entrepreneurship and convergence papers, 1987; 11 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0024)
      Includes De Long, entrepreneurship, and convergence papers.
    - Entrepreneurship and Economic Growth, 2007 (Box 46)
    - Entrepreneurship and Innovation, 2006 (Box 47)
    - Entrepreneurship and Invention, 2005-2006; 2 folders (Box 26)
    - Entrepreneurship and the Long Run Productivity Record, 1985 (Box 5)
    - Entrepreneurship and the Sociopolitical Climate, 1981 (Box 3)
    - Entrepreneurship and the Sociopolitical Climate, 1983 (Box 29)
    - Entrepreneurship and the sociopolitical climate, 1981 (Box 47)
    - Entrepreneurship in Economic Theory, 1968 (Box 47)
    - Entrepreneurship Prize Acceptance Speech, 2003 (Box 47)
    - Entrepreneurship Research and Teaching, 2005 (Box 25)
    - Entrepreneurship, Innovation and Growth, 2002 (Box 26)
      Copy and reprint
    - Entrepreneurship: Productive, Unproductive, and Destructive, 1989; 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Entrepreneurship: Productive, Unproductive, and Destructive (reprint), 1990 (Box 37)
    - Entrepreneurship: Productive, Unproductive, and Imitative or the Rule of the Rules of the Game, 1987-1990 (Box 47)
      Reprint and drafts
    - Environmental Industries with Substantial Start-Up Costs as Contributions to Trade Competitiveness, 1995 (Box 47)
    - Environmental Industries with Substantial Start-up costs as contributors to Trade Competitiveness, 1995 (Box 24)
      Proofs and drafts
    - Environmental Industries with Substantial Start-up costs as contributors to Trade Competitiveness, 1995 (Box 25)
    - Environmental Protection, International Spillovers and Trade, Wicksell Lecture, 1971 (Box 47)
    - Equity vs Allocative Efficiency: Toward A Theory of Distributive Justice, 1978 (Box 47)
    - Erik Lundberg Memorial Article, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Error Produced by Linearization, 1967 (Box 47)
    - Escalated Economy and the Stimulating Effects of Inflation, 1965 (Box 47)
    - Essay for Herbert Simon Festschrift "On Rational Satisficing", 2004 (Box 47)
    - Essay on Daniel Patrick Moynihan, 2003 (Box 47)
    - Essays in Honor of Samuel Hollander, 2001 (Box 25)
    - External Economies and Second-Order Optimality Conditions, 1964-1970; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Factor-Price Equalization Model and Industry Labor Productivity: An Empirical Test Across Countries, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Farm Families Project, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Feedback between Information Production and Productivity Growth: A Chaos Model, 1985 (Box 6)
    - Feedback Between R&D and Productivity Growth: A Chaos Model, 1986 (Box 47)
    - Feedback from Productivity Growth to R, 1983 (Box 26)
    - Feedback from Productivity Growth to R and D, 1983 (Box 37)
    - Feedback from Productivity Growth to R&D, 1983 (Box 47)
    - Feedback Models: R and D, Information and Productivity Growth, 1983; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Feedback Models: R and D, Information and Productivity Growth, 1983 (Box 6)
    - Feedback Models: R and D, Information and Productivity Growth, 1983 (Box 14)
      Copyright agreement and proofs
    - Feedback Models: R&D, Information, and..., 1983; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Feltrinelli Prize: The Unmatched Economic Development of the Past Two Centuries, 2005 (Box 25)
    - Files for an unidentified research paper, 1987; 17 document files (Lotus 1-2-3 format); less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0022)
      Title of paper is unclear from files.
    - Files for multiple papers on productivity and education, 1983-1986; 9 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0110)
    - Files for paper on art investment and draft article for the Wall Street Journal, 1983-1987; 19 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0115)
    - Files for papers on dumping and Lionel Robbins, 1983-1986; 9 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0112)
    - Files for papers on productivity growth, performing arts, and ticket prices on Broadway, 1983-1986; 5 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0106)
    - Files for papers on retail and methods in economics, 1983; 15 text files; less than 1 MB. (Digital-materials RL00092-SET-0001, Disk RL00092-FL5-0111)
    - Financial Incentives to Alleviate Difficult Social Problems, 1984 (Box 3)
    - Financial Prospects for the Performing Arts: Report from the Cloudy Crystal Ball, 1980 (Box 4)
    - Firm with Inelastic Demands, 1970 (Box 47)
    - Firm's Optimal Debt-Equity Combination and the Cost of Capital, 1967 (Box 47)
    - Firms with Limited Money Capital, 1953 (Box 47)
    - Five Camera-Demand Models: A Guide for non-specialists, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Fixed Costs, Sunk Costs, Entry Barriers, and Sustainability of Monopoly, 1981 (Box 47)
    - Foreword for Kauffman Foundation Book, 2009 (Box 47)
    - Formal Entrepreneurship Theory in Economics: Existence and Bounds, 1993 (Box 6)
    - Formal Entrepreneurship Theory in Economics: Existence and Bounds, 1993 (Box 47)
    - Formal Microeconomic Structure for Innovative Entrepreneurship Theory, 2011 (Box 47)
    - Formalisation of Mr. Harrod's Model, 1949 (Box 47)
    - Forms for Empirical Cost Functions to Evaluate Efficiency of Industry Structure, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Fortune Encyclopedia, 1992 (Box 47)
    - Four sources of innovation and stimulation of growth in the Dutch Economy, 2004; 2 folders (Box 37)
      Proofs, drafts, and related correspondence
    - Four Sources of Innovation and Stimulation of Growth in the Dutch Economy, 2004 (Box 47)
    - Free Markets and Rational Regulation: The Indispensable Formula for Prosperity and Growth, Undated (Box 25)
    - Full Costing, Competition and Regulatory Practice, 1973 (Box 47)
    - Further Opportunities for Cost Reduction of Medical Care, 2010 (Box 25)
    - Further Opportunities for Cost Reduction of Medical Care, 2010 (Box 47)
    - Future of the Theater and the Cost Disease of the Arts, 1987 (Box 4)
    - Future of the Theatre and the Cost Disease of the Arts, 1984 (Box 84)
    - Global Competition and Comparative Advantage, 2006 (Box 26)
    - Globalization: Prospects, Promise and Problems, 2003 (Box 38)
    - Good News? Health and Education costs are rising rapidly, 1993 (Box 37)
    - Government as a catalyst for private pursuit of Social Goals, 1982 (Box 47)
    - Growth Policy and the Services, 1983 (Box 47)
    - Growth, the market and dissemination of technology, 1991 (Box 6)
    - Growth, the market and dissemination of technology, 1991 (Box 25)
    - Guest Workers and Income Transfer Programs Financed by Host Governments, 1979 (Box 47)
    - Having Your Cake: How to Preserve Universal-Service Cross Subsidies While Facilitating Competitive Entry, 1999 (Box 47)
    - Health care, education and the cost disease: a looming crisis for public choice, 1993 (Box 47)
    - Health Care as a Handcraft Industry, 1995 (Box 47)
    - Health Care, Education and the Cost Disease, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Herbert Simon festschrift, 2003 (Box 47)
    - Historical Perspectives on the International Convergence of Productivity, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Horizontal Collusion and Innovation, 1991 (Box 4)
    - How Arbitrary is 'Arbitrary'? - or Toward the Deserved Demise of Full Cost Allocation, 1987 (Box 3)
    - How Arbitrary is 'Arbitrary'? - or Toward the Deserved Demise of Full Cost Allocation, 1987 (Box 47)
    - How Regulations can be misled by simplistic theory, 2005 (Box 26)
    - How to think about rising college costs, 2005 (Box 37)
      Draft and related correspondence
    - Hypotheses on Routinization of Innovation, Foreign Competition and Income Distribution, 1997; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Impact of the Broadway Theatre on the Economy of New York City, 1977 (Box 18)
    - Imperatives of the Fuel Crises, 1979 (Box 47)
    - Importance of Energy Profitability, 1982 (Box 26)
    - Incentives for Solving Social Problems, 1984 (Box 29)
    - Income and Substitution Effects in the Linder Theorem, 1973 (Box 47)
    - Income Distribution Frontier and Taxation of Migrants, 1982 (Box 47)
    - Incremental Costs, Pricing and the Differential "Fully Allocated Cost" Proposal, 1966 (Box 48)
    - Industrial Productivity, 1991 (Box 48)
    - Industrial Productivity, 1991 (Box 4)
    - Industry Structure Analysis and Public Policy, 1983 (Box 48)
    - Inefficient and Locally Stable Trade Equilibria Under Scale Economies, 1996 (Box 48)
    - Inflation and the Performing Arts, 1984 (Box 29)
      Copy of article co-authored with Hilda Baumol
    - Information, Business and Productivity Growth, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Information, Computers, and the Structure of Industry, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Information, Technology and the Service Sector: A Feedback Process?, 1985-1986; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Informed Judgement, Rigorous Theory and Public Policy, 1965 (Box 48)
      Reprint and proof
    - Innovation and Creative Destruction, 2001 (Box 26)
    - Innovation and Entrepreneurship: The David-Goliath Symbiosis, 2002 (Box 48)
    - Innovation and growth: two common misapprehensions, 2003 (Box 48)
    - Innovation and its Effects on International Trade, 2004 (Box 48)
    - Innovation and Strategic Sabotage as a Feedback Process, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Innovation and strategic sabotage as a feedback process, 1992 (Box 48)
    - Innovations as Essential Facilities for Competition and Growth, 1999 (Box 25)
    - Innovative Entrepreneurship: Education that Helps Education that Handicaps, undated (Box 48)
    - Innovative Entrepreneurship: is there Education that Helps and Education that Handicaps?, 2007 (Box 25)
    - Input and Output Composition Changes, 1984 (Box 48)
    - Input and Output Composition Changes: Measuring the Effect on the Productivity Slowdown, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Input choices and rate-of-return regulation: an overview of the discussion, 1970 (Box 48)
    - Integer Programming and Pricing, 1960 (Box 48)
    - Intellectual Property: how the right to keep it to yourself promotes dissemination, 2005 (Box 38)
    - Interactions Between Successive Polling Results and Voting Intentions, 1957 (Box 48)
    - Interconnection Prices: Making telephone competition a reality, 1998 (Box 23)
    - Interconnection prices: making telephone competition a reality, 1999 (Box 48)
    - International Convergence of Productivity, 1992 (Box 25)